[
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p2v1",
  "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_01",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99D_MSQ_10",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_objective_title",
  "Description": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99E_MSQ_01_EnterEdengrove_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99E_Morgaine_p2v1_01",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc1"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p6",
  "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_02",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_01",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_objective_title",
  "Description": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99E_MSQ_02_MyrddinClues_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc2"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p10",
  "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_03",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_02",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_objective_title",
  "Description": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99E_MSQ_03_CollectSamples_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc1"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p7",
  "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_04",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_03",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_objective_title",
  "Description": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99E_MSQ_04_MotherwellClues_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc1"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Galahad_p3a",
  "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_05",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_04",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_objective_title",
  "Description": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99E_MSQ_05_UnlockPrison_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc2"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p6v2",
  "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_06",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_05",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_objective_title",
  "Description": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99E_MSQ_06_MyrddinsPrison_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc2"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p14",
  "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_07",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_06",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_objective_title",
  "Description": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99E_MSQ_07_RetrieveHeadpiece_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc2"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Sun_p15",
  "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_08",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_07",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_objective_title",
  "Description": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99E_MSQ_08_AdianaPermission_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc1"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p2v2",
  "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_09",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_objective_title",
  "Description": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc3"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_alt",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Morgaine_p2v2",
  "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_09",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_08",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_alt_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_objective_title",
  "Description": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99E_MSQ_09_TheMotherwell_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc3"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "99E_Yash_p3",
  "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_10",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_09",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_objective_title",
  "Description": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99E_MSQ_10_ToCaerDun_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true,
  "QuestArcTag": "EdengroveV2Arc3"
 },
 {
  "ObjectiveID": "99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector",
  "Type": "MainStoryQuest",
  "Task": "99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_container",
  "NpcDestinationId": "0717_Warden",
  "AchievementId": "99E_MSQ_11",
  "RequiredAchievementId": "99E_MSQ_10",
  "SuccessGameEventId": "99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_success",
  "CanBeAbandoned": false,
  "Title": "99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_objective_title",
  "Description": "99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_objective_desc",
  "PlayerPrompt": "99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_start_prompt",
  "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_proposal",
  "InProgressResponse": "99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_incomplete",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
  "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "99E_MSQ_11_ShatteredVector_complete_available_response",
  "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": true
 }
]